bevnetwork.com 2015-06-10

# » Privacy Policy Beverage Media Group

## Privacy Policy

Beverage Media Group, Inc. takes your personal information very seriously. Please read this privacy policy carefully, as it describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit our Web site.

In order to supply you with Beverage Media Group, Inc.’s services, we need certain information from you, such as your e-mail address, telephone number, mailing address and, in some instances, credit card number. We protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information you input. Beverage Media Group, Inc. will never sell, rent or share this private information, including your e-mail address, with any third parties.

Beverage Media Group, Inc. uses browser cookies, parcels of text placed on your computer’s hard drive by our server, to facilitate access to your subscriber profile.

As part of Beverage Media Group, Inc.’s package, we may offer links allowing visitors access to third party sites. Beverage Media Group, Inc. is not responsible for the content appearing on those sites. Additionally, third-party advertisers may also place their own unique cookie on your browser. Please consult the individual privacy policies of those sites for more details on user information.

All information provided to Beverage Media Group, Inc. is stored on secure database servers.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Beverage Media Group, Inc., please contact us at [info@bevmedia.com](mailto:info@bevmedia.com).
